BUILDING STRONG BRAND TO EMPOWER YOUR BUSINESS

NICE TO MEET YOU

YAROSLAVA BYKOVA Brand & PR expert

brand strategy | positioning | reputation | legacy

"My inspiration is always about facing new life challenges"

Age: 27 From: Kyiv Currently in: Lviv







ABOUT

I am an experienced PR and Brand developer with a strong background of helping companies' reputation and brand become stronger. Areas I've faced with so far: agribusiness, law and IT.

Being an open-minded, creative and extremely honest person lets me build strong relationships with my team. Never afraid of any challenges and deadlines.

EMPLOYMENT



2019-2020 Branding&Marketing Specialist → Brand&PR Lead inVerita (full-time)



2019-2020 Brand Development Manager QU'ARTE design (part-time)



2015 - 2018 PR-specialist → Deputy Chief land manager of the Western region in social work and PR AgroGeneration (full-time)



2015 - 2016 PR Manager The Bleyzer Foundation (part-time)



EDUCATION

2009-2015

Master's degree: Mass Communications

University: NTUU "Igor Sikorsky Kyiv Polytechnic Institute" (Kyiv)

CERTIFICATES:

- 2018 «OktenWeb University» SEO optimisation course (Lviv)
- 2018 4Smart business academy «Effective HR» (Lviv)
- 2016 Sterling Business School: Lean Six Sigma (Lviv)
- 2015 LSE (London School of English) Certificate of Advanced English (Kyiv)

SKILLS

- Brand development
- Positioning
- Corporate communications
- Public speaking
- Strategic planning
- Negotiations
- Copywriting
- Proofreading and editing

INTERESTS













snorts